You know, this all started when you got here.
People are going missing. Do you know anything about this?
What is it you've been doing on the side when you're not working?
Thank you.
Isn't it?
Answer me at once, Makio.
Answer me at once.
I almost forgot why I came here in the first place.
I'm supposed to be looking for Mr. Uzui's wife, Miss Hinatsuro.
Laying the shamisen and Koto probably won't help much with doing that.
But it's not like anything else is happening here.
I've been all years since I arrived, and I still haven't heard a word about Miss Hinatsuro.
Then again, the owner of this house died two days ago.
Which makes sense why everyone is somber around here.
I can't find my back.
That's no good.
A young girl is crying.
Huh?
Someone is coming this way.
Ogimoto house certainly has no shortage of headaches.
I've got to find a way to let Lord Tengen know what happened.
Before it's too late.
If you cause a scene, I'll have your insides ground up into a bloody pulp.
That must be the food that woman left for her.
Which means that room must be Makio's.
It's weird.
Her food's still there.
Is she sick or in trouble?
I can't tell.
Something creepy's going on, that's for sure.
Here I am, sitting around doing nothing!
That's not my style!
There's wind.
Even though the windows are closed.
The attic.
Hey! Tower!
I'm onto you!
What the...
Now I just have to catch the damn thing before it gets away.
It's a demon for sure.
But where's it heading?
I can hardly keep up.
Get out of the way!
Get back here!
What's going on?
It's daytime, so it has to stay up there.
But it's gotta come down using the walls at some point.
Like right now!
Where are you off to in a rush, good look?
Did you knock him out?
Damn it, that was too early.
Now it's headed downstairs.
Downstairs!
This way!
No wait!
This way?
I can't tell.
It's hard to get a feel for it.
Where is that thing?
I can't believe I lost it!
Those idiots got in my way!
Hey! What the hell happened here?
Seriously! Your room's a mess!
Wait!
Did you get in a fight?
Are you okay?
Who did this?
Hey, don't cry.
What's going on? You alright?
Sorry I yelled like that.
I wasn't angry or anything.
I swear.
It's just...
I was surprised, that's all.
You there.
What do you think you're doing in my room?
That sound...
That's not a human standing behind me.
That's a demon.
I didn't even notice she was there until she started speaking.
How is that possible?
This sound is bad news.
I've never heard one so ominously quiet before.
Which means...
This...
Is an upper rank demon.
What's wrong?
Are you hard of hearing or something, girl?
Please wait, Ouroon Warabe-Hime.
That girl is brand new.
She just started here the day before yesterday.
And?
So what if she's new?
Forgive me if I intruded.
I saw this room was a mess.
And I heard a girl crying in here.
Why are you so damn hideous?
My goodness.
What?
Looking at you makes me ill.
Girls like you are better off dead.
Also, what's with that hair color?
You look like a sore thumb.
In any case, you're right.
This room is still in shambles, isn't it?
If I'm not mistaken, I told you to clean it up.
Shut your mouth!
Stop all that screaming!
And start cleaning, brat!
I'm sorry.
Forgive me, Ouroon.
I'll clean it all up.
Just please let go!
What's this?
Please.
Take your hands off her.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
Thanks, Daniel.
Great.
Goodbye.
Zuidu.
We've decided to raid.
We Brig combat to siellä.
This is a very good assignment.
We were to stay trained to be on our side.
This one was full.
All done.
I made sure to scrub down all of the hallways.
Oh, right.
The flowers.
They're all prepared.
What?
Already?
Anything else I can do to help?
Well, let me think.
Um...
Here's a fresh cup of tea.
What's next?
You didn't have to do that.
No problem.
So what's next?
I want to help.
Would you be quiet and hold on a second?
You're a quick worker.
And well behaved.
That girl is out of control.
She smashed a hole right through the wall.
It looks like I need to teach that one a hard lesson or two.
Listen, Inoko!
What on earth are you doing?
Even if I focus, I can't sense it at all.
Where the hell did that thing go?
What did you say to me?
I dare you to say that again.
Please, take your hands off of her.
Up close.
You're even uglier than I thought.
Take your...
Who do you think you are?
How dare you touch me?
Stop all this madness at once!
What do you mean?
The ones here who committed Ashinuke did so to escape your vile cruelty.
If that weren't enough, some have even been driven to take their own lives.
Enough is enough.
That is quite a serious accusation, madam.
You really think I'm the one to blame?
Help me to understand how it's not their fault for irritating me in the first place.
Until now, I've looked the other way more times than I can count.
But you're far too much trouble to just ignore.
There's no excusing it!
You forget yourself in my presence.
Whose earnings do you think allowed this house to prosper the way it has?
For years, you hag.
Those eyes of yours.
They remind me of a story I've heard.
An old lady from the tea house told it to me when I was young.
Her memory was beginning to decline.
But she would talk about a certain Oiran.
An Oiran who was as beautiful as she was twisted.
The old lady said she'd seen such women when she was a child.
And again when she reached middle age.
These Oirons were fond of assuming names ending with He-Men.
And if anything were to irritate them,
they'd cock their heads to the side and stick their nose up at you.
That was a unique habit that they shared.
Who are you?
What are you?
Could it be?
That's it.
You're not even human to begin with, are you?
Perhaps it wasn't obvious.
But that's the sort of thing you should keep your mouth shut about when you realize it.
That's the smartest way to live, don't you think?
That's how everyone survived, including me.
But it looks like you're far stupider than I could have imagined.
And now, you're staring death in the eye for that same stupidity.
It's such a pity, Omitsu.
What are you scared of?
There's no need for you to be afraid.
The dried-out flesh of old hags like you tastes revolting.
And you're hideous.
Why would I eat you?
I'm actually offended you assumed I would.
Goodbye, Omitsu.
Please!
SO-
What just happened?
Did you kill him?
She's dead!
She fell?
She killed him!
Did you kill me?
Is the middle of the non- remote?
She's bleeding!
Somebody manten't!
Wilson-
It's-
How are you doing, my dear?
Lord Muzan!
I see you've devoured a multitude of humans.
You've grown far more powerful than I anticipated.
You should be proud.
Yes, sir!
But you mustn't let your guard down.
When things go your way, they're more likely to slip through your fingers.
Understood, Lord Muzan.
A skilled Demon Slayer Corps member, like a Hashira, could recognize us as demons in mere seconds.
However, we, on the other hand, are quite different from capable Hashira,
and cannot see any stark differences between humans at a glance as they do.
We can still distinguish them, though, by their blood type,
as well as the diseases they carry and their genetic makeup.
Daki.
Yes, yes, Lord Muzan!
You know that I have high hopes for you in particular.
No one compares to your beauty and strength, Daki.
That's seven Hashira now, that you've killed.
Mark my words.
From here on out, you're going to become even stronger.
A ruthless killer.
You are an extraordinary demon.
How dare you lay a finger on me!
Keep your hands to yourself!
Rotten little brat.
Someone needs to discipline you, and harshly.
I'm more than happy to volunteer.
Oi, Ranwara Bihime.
I beg of you.
Please.
Please find a way to forgive her.
Customers will be arriving very soon, and we need you.
I'll see that she's reprimanded harshly.
You have my word.
I'm begging you.
I'll be humiliated tonight without you.
I suppose I was just a bit too harsh, seeing as she's a newcomer.
See that her wounds are looked at.
And please, Master, raise your head and stand up.
I'm the one who should be apologizing right now.
Lately, so many things have left me irritated, you see.
I'm heading off to work, so get this place tidied up.
Yes, of course!
Call for some help and get this room in order.
Don't do anything that would get on Oiran Warabihime's nerves.
That little brat.
Even though that girl is knocked out cold over there.
Her injuries are only minor, which must be a result of the defensive falling technique.
She's no civilian.
I bet she's with the Demon Slayer Corps.
That said, she doesn't have the skill of a Hashira.
It might have taken a bit longer than I expected, but it seems they've finally taken the bait.
Let's see what you've got, swordsmen.
I'd be more than happy to devour every one of you.
What an unsettling smell.
At night in this city.
There's a murky scent in the air.
Thank you.
愛して燃え尽きてゆく 繰り返し繰り返し 血を流す魂が 夢を見るその先に 輝いて輝いて 新しい朝が来る 希望が花びく
Oh yeah 君を呼んでいる
Senko?
Zinko!
Thank goodness!
Are you alright, Zinko?
What just happened?
After you got punched, you blacked out, Zinko! We were worried sick!
Oh...
That's right. I'm just a bit dizzy is all. I had the weirdest dream I had become a man, ha ha!
We brought you some food, Zinko! So eat up!
And use this to keep the swelling down.
You gonna be okay?
Yeah. It's not as bad as it looks, I think.
Thank you... for earlier.
Huh?
This only happened because you defended me.
Well, of course I did. Any man would rescue a girl in need, isn't that right?
Not that I'm a man or anything, just that any human would do it!
Especially if you're the oldest daughter, like I am!
That's why I can't just stand by while a younger girl is crying!
But that's not true at all. Everyone here is busy, just trying to take care of themselves each day.
This is the very first time we've met someone, kind as you.
See you around the house, Zinko!
Please take care of yourself and get lots of rest, okay?
Right. Thank you so much.
Thank you so much.
Junior high and high school. Kimetsu Academy Story Christmas Arc!
At last! Today's the day I've been waiting for!
I've invited Nezuko to the Christmas party.
Thanks to my keen planning, we can proceed straight from the party to the wedding.
That must be her!
Nezuko's here!
I've been waiting for you!
Thank you for the party invite!
You're lucky I showed up!
Merry Christmas.
So what is Christmas anyway? Tell me!
Hey, I never even invited you guys!
And what's with those outfits?
Talk about ruining my plans, you jerks!
None of you have ever been invited to a Christmas party, am I right?
Stop fooling around! Everyone except Nezuko go home!
What did you say? Tell me what Christmas is, dammit!
Shut up, idiot!
I really Robinson do.
So...
Hi...
...